

<u> tristan.libeau@gmail.com</u>

• Pyrmont, NSW, Sydney, 2009, Australia

+61 451 962 593

Details

Driving license Full License (Australian) Nationality French

Date / Place of birth 14/12/1992 / Nantes

Profile

I am currently seeking a position as a Sales Person in a dynamic organization, which focuses on driving initiatives that greatly improve Profit and Customer satisfaction. With over 7 years professional hospitality industry experience, I am committed to customer satisfaction utilizing my exceptional communication skills. I am dedicated, passionate and strive to give my best to all projects. I am available Monday to Sunday, 38h to 40h a week.

Employment History

Barista / Supervisor, Belluci, Sydney

June 2018 — Present

- Quickly and accurately handled financial transactions of all types.
- Trained new employees on store policies and procedures.
- Remained knowledgeable about food industry trends and cultures.

Real Estate Agent, Cubecorp, Sydney

March 2018 — August 2019

- In charge of promoting and selling new off the plan project
- · House inspection
- · Showroom inspection

Barista, Romolo Espresso Cucina

August 2017 — January 2018

- In charge of the floor
- In charge of training new staff
- Plan and improves menu with the manager regularly
- Provided excellent customer service
- Up-Selling

Bar Attendant, Sokyo - The Star Casino (World Best bar qualified by Forbes), Sydney

February 2016 — August 2017

- Monitored bar inventory and made notes for needed supplies when necessary.
- · Built positive rapport with guests.
- Utilized excellent public speaking skills.

Food and Beverage Attendant, Harvest Buffet - The Star Casino, Sydney

September 2015 — February 2016

- Maintained a neat, organized, and safe working environment.
- Performed all duties in accordance with Food Handling Procedures.
- · Ensured sanitation and safety of units.

Food and Beverage Attendant, InterContinental, Sydney

March 2015 — September 2015

- Maintained strong work relationships with all hotel departments.
- Responsible for the set up of the bar and the main floor
- Performed all duties in accordance with Food & Beverage Handling Procedures.

Waiter and Bartender, Prince de Galles, a Luxury Collection Hotel, Paris

March 2013 — January 2015

- · Cash Handling
- · Improved my knowledge of French wines
- · In charge of cocktails production

Bartender, Hôtel Barrière L'Hermitage, La Baule-Escoublac

July 2011 — November 2012

- In charge of cocktails production, responsible for the set up of the bar
- · Devised and implemented improvements concerning menus
- In charge of orders from the suppliers
- · Cash handling
- · In charge of the stock take

Education

Barman Certification, Saint-Anne School - Saint-Nazaire, France

September 2011 — June 2012

http://www.lycee-sainte-anne.fr/FR/index.awp

High School Certificate in Hospitality, Saint-Anne School - Saint-Nazaire, France

September 2007 — July 2010

http://www.lycee-sainte-anne.fr/FR/index.awp

Skills

Ability to Multitask Adaptability

Communication Ability to Work Under Pressure

Leadership Skills Computer Skills

Internships

Hospitality Internship Program, Food and Beverage, Sydney

January 2021 — January 2021

- Duration 52 weeks
- Visa 402

References

References available upon request